macconnection.com 2009-12-19

# Mac Connection - Privacy Policy

We're committed to protecting your right to privacy. This Privacy Policy describes how we manage the personal information we collect while doing business. This Privacy Policy covers only information that is collected through the biz.pcconnection.com web site or other web site addresses that are operated by and provide service of PC Connection (the "Site"). This Privacy Policy does not cover information that may be collected through other web sites accessible through our Site or through software downloaded from our Site.

##    
Information We Collect Automatically When You Visit Our Site

_Cookies:_ When you visit our Site, a permanent "cookie" (a small text file) is stored on your computer's hard drive. The purpose of the cookie is to recognize you as a return visitor the next time you visit, so we can enhance and customize your online shopping experience. Cookies do not contain any personally identifiable information, and we do not use cookies to identify customers. You may set your Internet browser to reject cookies, but doing so will prevent our Site from operating as intended, and you will not be able to view the entire Site. Browsers may vary, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences.

_Log files:_ To enhance the quality of your experience during your visit to the Site, we also collect certain technical information from your computer each time you request a page during a visit to our Site and store it in log files. This information may include your Internet Protocol (IP) address, your computer's operating system, browser type, the addresses of pages you visit before and after visiting our Site, the date and time of your visit, and which pages you view during your visit to the Site.

_Clear gifs:_ The Site uses a software technology called clear gifs (also known as "web beacons" or "web bugs") that uses tiny graphics to record which pages are viewed by a Site visitor. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user's computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on web pages as they are displayed and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. Clear gifs do not contain any personally identifiable information, and we do not use them to identify individual customers.

_Profiles:_ We store information that we collect through cookies, log files, clear gifs, and/or third party sources to create a "profile" of your preferences. Together with your purchasing history, email address and other information you provide to us, we use your profile to reduce the steps needed for you to place orders through the Site, to provide tailored promotions and marketing offers, and to analyze and improve the content of our Site.

##    
Information We Collect When You Request or Order Our Products and Services

We collect different types of personal information for different purposes.

_Catalogs:_ When you request a catalog, we collect your name and mailing address so we can fulfill your request. We also request your email address and phone number.

_Log-in Identification:_ Individual consumers may register a log-in name and set a password when visiting our Site or placing an order through our Site. To register, we request that you provide your name, mailing address, telephone/fax numbers, and e-mail address. This registration enables us to track online orders and save your customer information and preferences so you won't have to re-enter the same information every time you return to our Site. We also use this information to authenticate your identity when you request access to our online services.

Business customers need a log-in name and password to access their Internet Business Accounts. To obtain a login name, you must provide your PC Connection account number, company name, department, mailing address, telephone/fax numbers, and the names, telephone/fax numbers and e-mail addresses of all authorized buyers associated with the account. This information allows us to quickly process orders, provide efficient customer service, and present information relevant to a user's organization.

_Orders:_ To process and ship your order, we need your name, phone number, credit card account information, billing address, shipping address, and e-mail address. This information is stored on a secure server to allow us to process subsequent orders more quickly. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you.

_Contests and Surveys:_ When we offer a contest or survey through our Site, we generally request contact information and some demographic (such as zip code) information. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose the information. We will use this information to notify contest winners and award prizes, to improve our product offerings, and to assess the interests of those who visit our Site. Participants may receive periodic email notices about special offers and site updates.

##    
Communications from Us or the Site

We may use your contact information to respond to your requests or to communicate about your orders.

_Distribution Lists:_ Upon requesting a catalog, ordering our products/services, or participating in our online contests or surveys, you will be placed on our distribution lists and may receive occasional postal mail, email, or telephone notification about PC Connection products, services, special offers, promotions, or Site updates that we believe may be of interest to you. To remove yourself from these lists, see "Choice" below.

_Emails:_ In order to create a better electronic community, we may collect specific user profile information, such as the referring URL, when you click on a link in our e-mail communications. This information is used to capture broad demographic trends that may allow us to provide you with information better tailored to your interests. You will not be personally identified from this information. To opt out of these emails, see "Choice" below.

##    
Conditions Under Which We Share Information

We may disclose customer information for the purposes described below, or for other purposes that you authorize:

      _Our Agents, Service Providers and Contractors:_ We engage third parties to perform certain of our business operations for which customer information may be disclosed. For example, we use outside shipping companies to fulfill orders and credit card processing companies to obtain payment for our goods and services. We also disclose customer information to third parties that perform other tasks or functions, such as order processing and fulfillment, customer relations, technical support, training, marketing/advertising, legal, fraud prevention services and fraud risk modeling, and other administrative, professional, or consulting services. We allow these third parties to make further disclosures of your personally identifiable information only with your consent or as permitted under this Privacy Policy.

        _Third Party Products and Services:_ We may occasionally share your name and contact information with companies whose products and services may be of interest to you. Out of respect for your privacy, we allow you to opt-out of having your information shared with third parties for this purpose, as described under "Choice" below.

      _Other Disclosures:_ We may collect, maintain, and disclose your information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights or property; to protect the rights, property, or safety of other persons; to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on us or the Site. We may also disclose your information in connection with an actual or proposed corporate transaction or insolvency proceeding involving all or part of the business or assets to which the information pertains.

      _Aggregate (Non-Personally Identifiable) Information:_ Information about you and your activities on our Site may be aggregated, or grouped together, with information about other customers in a way such that your information cannot be identified as yours. We may disclose this aggregate information to third parties that perform data collection and reporting services regarding our customers' activities on our Site, measure the effectiveness of our marketing efforts, or evaluate the interests and preferences of people in certain categories. These third parties may use cookies on our Site and may receive anonymous information about your browsing and purchasing activity on our Site.

##    
Choice

You may opt out of certain uses of your personal information, as described above.

_Mail and Telephone Lists:_ To remove yourself from our promotional mailing and telephone lists, please send an e-mail to [mailinglist@pcconnection.com](mailto:mailinglist@pcconnection.com) or call us at 1-888-213-0260.

_Email Lists:_ If you prefer not to receive e-mail from us (other than those directly responsive to your orders, inquiries or requests), please click the "unsubscribe" link at the bottom of any promotional e-mail or send a blank email request to [unsubscribe@pcconnection.com](mailto:unsubscribe@pcconnection.com). Please note: Even though you may choose to unsubscribe from our email distribution list, for security reasons we will always attempt to send you transaction-related order, backorder and shipment confirmation emails concerning your purchases through the Site.

##    
Access and Amendment of Personal Information

You may request to access or delete your personal information and may request to make appropriate changes to it by sending a request to one of the addresses provided below under "Contact Us."

##    
Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card numbers) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

##    
Other Web Sites

We have no control over the privacy practices of web sites outside of our biz.pcconnection.com domain. If you follow a link to another site, read the site's privacy policy and contact the site's administrator with your privacy-related questions.

##    
Children's Privacy

We do not knowingly market to, accept orders from, or solicit personal information from children under the age of 13.

##    
Privacy Policy Changes

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. Any changes will be posted on the Site. Individuals may be asked to consent or may be given an opportunity to opt out before previously collected information is used for purposes materially different from the purposes permitted under the Privacy Policy in effect at the time the information was originally collected.

##    
Contact Us

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at: Pam Carter, 730 Milford Rd., Merrimack, NH 03054; [pcarter@pcconnection.com](mailto:pcarter@pcconnection.com); ph. 603-683-2753.

##    
California Residents

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits customers who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an e-mail request to [internetmarketing@pcconnection.com](mailto:internetmarketing@pcconnection.com) or write to us at Internet Marketing, 730 Milford Rd., Merrimack, NH 03054.

**Effective Date** January 17, 2007

© Copyright PC Connection, Inc. 2007. All rights reserved.
